<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nicdao_Exer02</string>
    <string name="title_text">Which Marvel Character Are You?</string>
    <string name="marvel_logo">The Marvel Logo</string>
    <string name="start_button">START</string>
    <string name="retry_button">RETRY</string>
    <string name="bio">FIND OUT THE INNER HERO IN YOU</string>
    <string name = "antman">Scott Edward Harris Lang is a former criminal
        who had been convinced by Hank Pym to take on the mantle as Ant Man,
        in order for them to then prevent Darren Cross from attempting to manipulate
        the Pym Particles to create extremely weapons, which he would then sell to
        HYDRA and the Ten Rings. Lang was trained up by Hope van Dyne and Pym to
        master the Ant-Man technology, before he was sent to steal the Yellowjacket
        Suit from Cross.</string>
    <string name = "blackpanther">TChalla is the King of Wakanda and first son of
        TChaka and Ramonda. As the Wakandan monarch, he became the holder
        of the Black Panther mantle. Following the death of his father in the
        bombing attack orchestrated by Helmut Zemo, TChalla had set out to kill
        the Winter Soldier, who was widely believed to be responsible for the attack.
        </string>
    <string name = "blackwidow">Natalia Alianovna "Natasha" Romanoff, also known as Black Widow, was
        one of the most talented spies and assassins in the entire world and a founding member of the
        Avengers. Originally a KGB operative and dangerous assassin, Romanoff was recruited into S.H.I.E.L.D.
        by Clint Barton.</string>
    <string name="captainamerica">Captain Steven Grant "Steve" Rogers is a World War II veteran,
        a founding member of the Avengers, and Earths first superhero. Rogers had suffered from
        numerous health problems, and upon Americas entry into World War II, was rejected from the
        service within United States Army despite several attempts to enlist.</string>
    <string name="drstrange">Stephen Vincent Strange M.D., Ph.D is a powerful sorcerer and Master of
        the Mystic Arts. Originally a brilliant, although arrogant, neurosurgeon, Strange got into a car
        accident which resulted with his hands becoming crippled. When all Western medicine failed him,
        Strange embarked on a journey that led him into Kamar-Taj where Strange had made the discovery of
        magic and alternate dimensions, being trained by the Ancient One. </string>
    <string name = "hulk">Robert Bruce Banner is the son of Dr. Brian Banner, an atomic physicist, and his wife
        Rebecca. Although Rebecca deeply loved Bruce, who returned her affection, Brian hated their child. Brian
        never wanted children because of what happened to him and his sisters Susan and Elaine Banner. </string>
    <string name="ironman">Anthony Edward "Tony" Stark was a billionaire industrialist, a founding member of the
        Avengers, and the former CEO of Stark Industries. A brash but brilliant inventor, Stark was self-described
        as a genius, billionaire, playboy, and philanthropist. </string>
    <string name="spiderman">Peter Benjamin Parker is a high school student who gained spider-like abilities,
        fighting crime across New York City as the alter ego Spider-Man, hoping someday, he will live up to his
        heroes in the Avengers.</string>
    <string name="starlord">Peter Jason Quill is a Celestial-human hybrid who was abducted from Earth in
        1988 by the Yondu Ravager Clan, and afterwards began building a reputation as the notorious intergalactic outlaw,
        nicknamed Star-Lord. In 2014, he decided to leave the Ravagers and operate individually, starting by stealing a
        precious artifact known as the Orb, unintentionally becoming a key player in the Quest for the Orb. </string>
    <string name="thor">Thor Odinson is the Asgardian God of Thunder, the former king of Asgard and New Asgard, and a founding
        member of the Avengers. When his irresponsible and impetuous behavior reignited a conflict between Asgard and Jotunheim,
        Thor was denied the right to become king, stripped of his power, and banished to Earth by Odin.</string>
</resources>
